James E. and Barbara H. Sherman Ghost Town Photograph Collection circa 1865-1975 (bulk 1964-1969)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Research cards, circa 1964-1968; Series III
  - Silverbell, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Silver King, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Stanton, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Stockton, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Stoddard, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Sunnyside, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Swansea, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Tiger, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Tip Top, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Tombstone, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Total Wreck, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Troy, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Twin Buttes, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Vekol, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Venezia, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Virginia City, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Vulture City, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Washington Camp and Duquesne, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Weaver, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - White Hills, Ariz., circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General information Ariz. mines, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - General information, New Mexico mines, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Albemarle, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Allerton, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Allison, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Alma, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Amizette, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Andrews, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Baldy, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Black Hawk, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Bland, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Blossburg, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Bonanza City, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Bonito City, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Brilliant, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Cabezon, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Carbonateville, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Carlisle, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Carthage, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Catskill, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Cerrillos, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Chance City, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Chloride, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Clairmont, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Clarkville, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Cloverdale, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Coalora, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Colfax, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Columbus, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Cooks Peak, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Coolidge, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Cooney, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Copper City, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Copperton, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Council Rock, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Dawson, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Dolores, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Elizabethtown, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Engle, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Estey City, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Faywood Hot Springs, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Fleming, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Gamerco, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Gardiner, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Georgetown, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Gibson, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Glen-Woody, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Glorieta, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Gold Dust, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Golden, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Gold Hill, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Grafton, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Graham, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Hachita, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Hagan, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Hematite, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Hermanas, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Hermosa, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Hillsboro, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Jicarilla, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Johnson Mesa, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Kelly, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Kingston, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Koehler, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - La Bajada, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - La Belle, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Lake Valley, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - La Ventana, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Leopold, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Lincoln, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Madrid, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Malone, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Mentmore, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Midnight and Anchor, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Mineral Hill, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Modoc, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Mogollon, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Navajo, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Nutt, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Oak Grove, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Organ, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Orogrande, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Otero, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Park City, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Parsons, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Pascal, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Perryville, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Pinos Altos, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Pyramid, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Rabenton, NM, circa 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Red River, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Riley, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Robinson, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Rosedale, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Sacramento City, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - San Antonio, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - San Augustine, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - San Geronimo, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - San Marcial, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - San Pedro, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Santa Rita, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Sawyer, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Senorito, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Shakespeare, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Shandon, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Steins, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Sugarite, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Swastika, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Sylvanite, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Telegraph, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Tererro, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Tierra Blanca, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Tokay, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Trementina, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Twining, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Tyrone, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Valedon, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Van Houten, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Vera Cruz, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Virginia City, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Waldo, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - White Oaks, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Winston. NM (Fairview), 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Yankee, NM, 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Research cards, general information and locations not used in the book, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Research contacts, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Negatives, 1964-1969; Series IV
  - Negatives of book page layout, 3 1/2" x 4 1/2", undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 35mm negatives of the photographs in boxes 1 through 7, undated (Box 11)
- Published books and map, 1969, 1975; Series V
  - Map of Lincoln County, NM ghost towns, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ghost Towns of Arizona, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ghost Towns and Mining Camps of New Mexico, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)